<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8'?>
<gameList>
  <game>
    <path>./Quake 2.sh</path>
    <name>Quake II</name>
    <desc>A sequel in name only, this follow up to id's 1996 Quake, is a first-person shooter revolving around the Earth-Strogg war. The Strogg alien race threatens the Earth, but Earth has launched a counter-offensive, Operation Alien Overlord. Overlord takes the battle to the Strogg homeworld with the ultimate objective of securing their capital city and killing their ruler. As a FPS, Quake II contains a variety of weapons including the fall back Blaster, the Railgun, and the secret BFG10K. Health, armor, and ammunition pick-ups can be found during levels, as can the classic Quake's Quad Damage power-up. Game play involves mowing down alien opponents as the player progresses through levels, completing in-game objectives. Quake II also comes with multiplayer support for Deathmatches.</desc>
    <image>./quake2/cover.png</image>
    <releasedate>19971209T000000</releasedate>
    <genre>Shooter / 1st person-Shooter</genre>
    <developer>id Software</developer>
    <publisher>Activision</publisher>
  </game>
  <game>
    <path>./Quake 2 - Capture The Flag.sh</path>
    <name>Quake II - Capture The Flag</name>
    <image>./quake2/screenshot_q2ctf.jpg</image>
    <genre>Shooter / 1st person-Shooter</genre>
  </game>
  <game>
    <path>./Quake 2 - The Reckoning.sh</path>
    <name>Quake II - The Reckoning</name>
    <desc>Quake II Mission Pack: The Reckoning is an official mission pack released for Quake 2, developed by Xatrix Entertainment Inc. and released in May 30, 1998.  You are part of an elite commando [force] that must infiltrate a hostile alien city.  Once inside, you must scour industrial landscapes, crawl through waterways and air ducts, navigate treacherous canyons teeming with vicious mutants, stow away on an alien spacecraft, and destroy the enemy's secret moon base.</desc>
    <image>./quake2/screenshot_reckoning.jpg</image>
    <releasedate>19980530T000000</releasedate>
    <genre>Shooter / 1st person-Shooter</genre>
    <developer>Xatrix Entertainment</developer>
    <publisher>id Software</publisher>
  </game>
  <game>
    <path>./Quake 2 - Ground Zero.sh</path>
    <name>Quake II - Ground Zero</name>
    <desc>Take out the Big Gun sounded simple enough, except the Strogg were waiting. You, and a few marines like you, are the lucky ones. You've made it down in one piece and are still able to contact the fleet. The Gravity Well, the Strogg's newest weapon in its arsenal against mankind, is operational.</desc>
    <image>./quake2/screenshot_groundzero.jpg</image>
    <releasedate>19980901T000000</releasedate>
    <genre>Shooter / 1st person-Shooter</genre>
    <developer>Rogue Entertainment</developer>
    <publisher>id Software</publisher>
  </game>
  <game>
    <path>./Quake 2 - Zaero.sh</path>
    <name>Quake II - Zaero</name>
    <desc>Zaero is an unofficial mission pack for Quake II, set 20 years later, with new levels, weapons, and items, and a new final boss.</desc>
    <image>./quake2/screenshot_zaero.jpg</image>
    <releasedate>19981101T000000</releasedate>
    <genre>Shooter / 1st person-Shooter</genre>
    <developer>Team Evolve</developer>
    <publisher>Macmillan Digital Publishing USA</publisher>
  </game>
</gameList>
